<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TechNotes</title><link>https://www.technotes.org/</link><description>Recent content on TechNotes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.technotes.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://www.technotes.org/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.technotes.org/about/</guid><description>Introduction to TechNotes It’s often said that “the Internet gives us access to all of human knowledge,” but that now-mundane “fact” is far from true. A lot of important knowledge and data is still only kept in institutional memory and physical books, or is technically available online but practically hard to find, hard to use, hard to understand, and/or potentially restricted by patents or copyright. In other cases, we have access to so much information, changing at such a rapid pace, that it’s an overwhelming task to make sense of it.</description></item><item><title>Founding Team</title><link>https://www.technotes.org/team/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.technotes.org/team/</guid><description>Braden MacDonald, Co-founder Braden is a software developer and technology enthusiast. He is the co-founder and CEO of TechNotes and the CTO of OpenCraft. Prior to TechNotes, Braden&amp;rsquo;s most recent major project was LabXchange, an online platform from Harvard University which provides world-class life sciences education materials to the world on-demand and for free. Braden led the software development for the project, which went on to have over two million users in its first year and won the 2020 Open edX Prize for creating the most impactful technical project built with Open edX.</description></item><item><title>Frequently Asked Questions</title><link>https://www.technotes.org/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.technotes.org/faq/</guid><description>What is TechNotes? What are you building? See our vision at About TechNotes.
What&amp;rsquo;s the status of this project? As of April 2021: we are in the process of developing a prototype that gives a good demonstration (vertical slice) of what we want to build, and we are seeking funders and partners that want to be involved. In addition to seeking funding, we&amp;rsquo;re starting to build a core team, an advisory board, a board of directors, and strategic partnerships.</description></item></channel></rss>